<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>science on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/categories/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in science on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Science Overview</title>
      <link>/science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/science/</guid>
      <description>https://www.ixl.com/science/
https://phet.colorado.edu/en/simulations/browse
https://mysteryscience.com/
https://www.howtosmile.org/
https://climatekids.nasa.gov/
https://kids.frontiersin.org/
https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0885200617302442
In the United States, Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) topics have been increasingly recognized as appropriate and relevant for children to explore in early childhood settings (California Department of Education, 2012, Greenfield et al., 2009, McClure et al., 2017, National Science Foundation, 2013).
The study finds preschoolers to be “little engineers,” who use their serendipitous science exposure to develop reasoning skills and solve simple problems in the world around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Trips</title>
      <link>/science/fieldtrips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/science/fieldtrips/</guid>
      <description>Review   [Amazeum YOU] (https://www.amazeum.org/visit/amazeum-you/) Ann Arbor Hands-On Museum - STEM at Home Aquarium of the Bay - At Home Lessons Arizona Science Center - Online Learning Buffalo Museum of Science - Virtual Science Fair California Science Center - Stuck at Home Science Carnegie Science Center - Things to DO Chicago Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum - Recipes for Play at home Children&amp;rsquo;s Creativity Museum - Create @ Home Children&amp;rsquo;s Discovery Museum of San Jose - Virtual Museum Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Houston - A Virtual Playground for our Mind Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Indianapolis At Home Children’s Museum of Pittsburgh - Museum At Home COSI Connects CuriOdyssey Science Experiments for Kids  Discovery Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum - At Home Discoveries Discovery Museum (Acton, MA) - Discovery at Home and Teacher Resources for Distance Learning Discovery Place Stay-at-Home Science  Duluth Children’s Museum stay@home play@home  ECHO at Home Ecotarium - At Home Resources Explora - Try this at home Exploratorium Online Learning Franklin @ Home Great Lakes Science Center - Engage with us at home Hawaii Children’s Discovery Center At Home Homewood Science Center Virtual Programs ‘Imiloa Astronomy Center of Hawaii - ʻImiloa@Home Insights El Paso Science Center - STEM Activities To Do At Home The Jackson Hole Children’s Museum - PlayCreateExplore*Discover at Home  Kansas Children&amp;rsquo;s Discovery Center - Discovery at home  Kohl Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum Home Zone and Teaching Resources  The Lawrence at Home  Lincoln Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum Boredom Busters  Macculloch Hall Historical Museum - Fun Activities for Home  Marbles Kids Museum - Play At Home  Michigan Science Center - Home Science Activities  Miami Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum - Museum At Home  Milton J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Experiments</title>
      <link>/science/experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/science/experiments/</guid>
      <description>WeAreTeachers.com  Website
Youtube Channel
 A lot of science experiments for K-8 Well explained with starting with the concepts to all the steps in the flow laid out clearly Divided into primary, elementary and middle schools categories Free printables to cut down on screen time    HowToSmile.org  [WebSite] (https://www.howtosmile.org/)
 Thousands of quality science activities is a valuable teacher resource Browse topics as the list is broad, narrow down the activities for appropriate grade and age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Videos</title>
      <link>/science/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/science/videos/</guid>
      <description>Youtube channels for science projects / topics  [Free School] (https://www.youtube.com/user/watchfreeschool): Introduce kids to famous art, literature and science in an age appropriate way
Mike Likes Science: Videos with a science and musical theme.
Science Channel: Channel on outer space, updated scientific exploration, earth science fundamentals.
Science Max: Science experiments you’ve done at home
Sema&amp;rsquo;s Lab: Experiments done at home by kids for kids.
[TheBrainScoop] (https://www.youtube.com/user/thebrainscoop): Field Museum in Chicago. Natural history museums with the world</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
