<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Learnosity on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Learnosity on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Selection Criteria</title>
      <link>/about/selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/selection/</guid>
      <description>Learnosity aims to reports on the pedagogy ideas and technologies that shape the future of education in the post Covid-19 world.
Learnosity was founded in 2020 by a parent and a techie to connect the community of parents with education technology entrepreneurs and their products. The site is built to fulfil the project requirement for the course offering CS 6460 (EdTech) at Georgia Institute of Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>360° learning</title>
      <link>/about/360degree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/360degree/</guid>
      <description>The 2019 K-12 School Giants Report shows that many K-12 districts across the country are emphasizing hands-on, practical and personalized learning. Educators and parents recognize the need for better career and technical education that is aligned with future vocations in STEM, business, and skilled trades. As a result, 360-degree learning has emerged as one of the latest trends in K-12 education. Traditional curricula need to be revisited and better aligned with hands-on programs and activities so that students are set for success in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggest a Program/Product</title>
      <link>/about/suggest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/suggest/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t see a popular EdTech product here? Send an email to rsethi32@gatech.edu with details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring programs</title>
      <link>/about/mentor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/mentor/</guid>
      <description>Learnosity explores youth mentoring programs in the country. Several best practices are found to increase effect sizes in mentoring programs.
 Monitoring of program implementation Screening of prospective mentors Matching of mentors and youth on the basis of one or more relevant criteria Both pre-match and ongoing training Supervision for mentor Support group for mentors Structured activities for mentors and youth Parent support or involvement components Expectations for both frequency of contact and length of relationship Mentor background in a helping role In addition, there are several mentor websites that suggest the inclusion of similar best practices with the hopes of created greater outcomes for youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>/about/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/feedback/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Inequality</title>
      <link>/about/divide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/divide/</guid>
      <description>Digital divide has increased hte social gap, thereby, making it impossible for students to receive quality education. The pandemic has exposed this harsh reality. Today, the most controversial and debated issue in education is lack of optimal computing resources in every household at an affordable cost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
