<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Showcase on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/showcase/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Showcase on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/showcase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Forestry.io</title>
      <link>/showcase/forestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/forestry/</guid>
      <description>It was clear from the get-go that we had to go with a static site generator. Static sites are secure, performant, and give you 100% flexibility. At Forestry.io we provide Content Management Solutions for websites built with static site generators, so we might be a little biased. The only question: Which static site generator was the right choice for us?
Why Hugo?  In our early research we looked at Ionic’s site to get some inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiply Employee Communications App</title>
      <link>/showcase/quiply-employee-communications-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/quiply-employee-communications-app/</guid>
      <description>With the launch of our Employee Communications app Quiply we created a very simple and static one-page website to showcase our product.
As our customer base and demand for marketing and communication started to grow, we needed a solution to easily grow and extend the contents of our web presence. As we do not have the need to serve dynamic content, we decided to use a static site generator. Amongst a couple of others, we tried Hugo and it became immediately clear that we&amp;rsquo;d use Hugo going forward as it compiles super-fast, is intuitive to use and offers all the features we need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo ShowcaseShowcase Template</title>
      <link>/showcase/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/template/</guid>
      <description>Have a notable Hugo site1? We would love to feature it in this Showcase Section
We would really appreciate if you could:
 Fork https://github.com/gohugoio/hugoDocs Run hugo new showcase/your-site (this requires &amp;gt;= Hugo 0.49). This will use the archetype bundle in the docs repo. Follow the instructions in the newly created page bundle. Create a new pull request in https://github.com/gohugoio/hugoDocs/pulls    We want this to show Hugo in its best light, so this is not for the average Hugo blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
