<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music Overview on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/music4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music Overview on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/music4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LessonFace</title>
      <link>/music4/lessonface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music4/lessonface/</guid>
      <description>Review  Lessonface.com
 Offers live online music lessons to students of all ages and levels for most instruments. Teachers approved through background checks. Parent encouraged to &amp;ldquo;sit in&amp;rdquo; in person or on the web session. COPPA-compliant, parents to sign up for kids under 13. Juilliard-trained teachers can prepare high schools students for auditions. Its not cheap though. Group lessons available at lower cost.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TakeLessons</title>
      <link>/music4/takelessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music4/takelessons/</guid>
      <description>Website  Take aways    TakeLessons is a startup that connects students with pre-screened music teachers, academic tutors, dance, acting, and foreign language instructors locally and online.
  Might take some effort to find the right teacher.
  Some complaints about their billing, so be careful.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thumbtack</title>
      <link>/music4/thumbtack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music4/thumbtack/</guid>
      <description>Take Aways Website
  Music lessons in real time, with a live coach.
  Parents can signup and choosing an instrument;
  The Find Teacher feature allows searching teachers by price range, availability, location etc.
  Video program is downloaded that helps video conference with the teacher in real time. 30-60 minute lessons
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube</title>
      <link>/music4/youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music4/youtube/</guid>
      <description>Take Aways Website
  Some of the best first steps to take in learning music is free lessons on youtube (without a doubt)
  Some kids feel very comfortable being able to skip back / replay videos and learn at their pace
  Some of the coaches use online platforms for 1-1 lessons and this helps children warn up to the coach by following their lessons on youtube first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
