<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reading Resources on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reading Resources on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Between the Lions</title>
      <link>/reading/between-the-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/between-the-lions/</guid>
      <description>This is a TV show that was introducewd on PBS in year 2000 with the aim of teaching children reading comprehension skill. It is targeted at kids who are beginning to read. Books are read on air during the program.
  This is also likey to be more appealing to the youngest readers (4 and 5 year olds)
  This program should be coupled with reading with the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OxfordOWL</title>
      <link>/reading/oxfordowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/oxfordowl/</guid>
      <description>  Pre-reading and beginning reading help for Pre-K to K readers through the pre-teen years. From phonics lessons to online books to story videos read by professional story tellers, this site offers comprehensive reading help and activities for educators and parents.
  Activities are included alongside e-books. Activities built to encourage reading. Books are linked to other similar books making discovery of new books easy.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBS Reading</title>
      <link>/reading/pbs-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/pbs-reading/</guid>
      <description>Take Aways    PBS reading is an educational and entertainment site full of games, videos, and quests featuring kids&#39; favorite PBS television show characters.
  Kids who are learning basic skills and already know many of the characters featured here from popular PBS shows such as Sesame Street and Curious George will enjoy playing games with their television friends.
  Parents are advised to sit next to kids and helping them learn safe and fun online skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Write Think</title>
      <link>/reading/readwritethink/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/readwritethink/</guid>
      <description>Take Aways    Reading through interactive practice.
  Activities provide a preview of the story line and related activities.
  Comic creator is a highlight of the site and helps children create comics. Students have to drag and drop their avatars, backgrounds and speech bubbles to create a story.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storyline (PreK, K, 1-2)</title>
      <link>/reading/storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/storyline/</guid>
      <description>Storyline Online streams reading videos that features kids and even celebrities reading books. The books usually have great accompanying illustrations. The books are categorized for various grade levels which makes it easier to find appropriate books for a student. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storynory</title>
      <link>/reading/storynory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/storynory/</guid>
      <description>Several book categories Great for children Easy to navigate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starfall</title>
      <link>/reading/starfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/starfall/</guid>
      <description>Take Aways    Starfall is a free web resource that uses fantasy as a tool to foster motivation in children. With a plot suited for you reader, it creates a sense of wonder and curiosity while reading.
  Learners engage with colorful characters through plots, musical, poems and activities. There are paid options to create custom custom worksheets, lessons, math sheets and more interactive games.
    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
