<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>math on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/categories/math/</link>
    <description>Recent content in math on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Math Overview</title>
      <link>/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/</guid>
      <description>Math is important and it’s important to help young children develop their mathematical thinking. A child’s math knowledge at the start of kindergarten predicts later academic achievement better than early reading or attention skills. Math is part of children’s everyday lives. Taking advantage of each of these math moments develops math learning. Each math moment is like a charging station that helps children become ready for more math learning. Math is measuring, sorting, building, noticing patterns, making comparisons, and describing the environment, as well as counting and knowing the names of shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrainPop Jr</title>
      <link>/math/brainpopjr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/brainpopjr/</guid>
      <description>BrainPOP Jr.   Specific videos and activities using the search tool, which categorizes content by subject, grade, and state or Common Core standards Short films are a terrific introduction to any topic. Use the videos to spark kids&#39; interest on a new topic or to reinforce what they&amp;rsquo;ve already learned in class Young animated hosts who speak directly to them with conversational and familiar language Characters narrate what&amp;rsquo;s happening, ask questions, provide examples, and define terms that may be difficult to grasp  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gracie &amp; Friends Birthday Cafe</title>
      <link>/math/gracie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/gracie/</guid>
      <description>Gracie &amp;amp; Friends Birthday Cafe    20 levels of birthday celebration gameplay
  Adaptive pacing to meet each child&amp;rsquo;s math level
  Multiple modes of scaffolding and support
  Aligns with research-based early math learning trajectories
  No in-app purchases
  No advertising
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IXL Math</title>
      <link>/math/ixl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/ixl/</guid>
      <description>IXL   Aligned to the Common Core State Standards or State standards Membership fees range from $9.95-$19.95 per month Math skills covered Continous Diagnostic tool helps identify what a student knows already and what they need to improve An app is available for iPad, Android, Chromebook, and Kindle Fire devices. Kids can try the skill exercises for free, but they&amp;rsquo;ll be limited to a small number of problems per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khan Academy Math</title>
      <link>/math/khan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/khan/</guid>
      <description>Khan Academy   Aligned to the Common Core State Standards Free Math skills covered Course Challenge tool helps assessments Kids can try the skill exercises for free    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Seeds</title>
      <link>/math/mathseeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/mathseeds/</guid>
      <description>Mathseeds   Mathseed has gamified the math lessons to make experience engaging Lessons are designed to drive home concepts through carefully scaffolded presentation and practice activities Program could be more adaptive in learning students mistakes and challenges and changing its course to drive point home    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matific</title>
      <link>/math/matific/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/matific/</guid>
      <description>Matific   Consists of engaging activities and games that are linked to content from the most popular math textbooks. Practice specific common core math skills individually Allows parents to assign specific challenges to students Good app for refreshing skills taught in the classroom Feedback is instant based on student performance Aligned with both USA Common Core and UK&amp;rsquo;s New National Math Curriculum    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore-Math</title>
      <link>/math/singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/singapore/</guid>
      <description>In typical U.S. math programs, students get a worked example, then solve problems that very closely follow that example, repeating all the same steps with different numbers.
Singapore math is a teaching method based on Singapore Ministry of Education national primary mathematics curriculum used for grade one through sixth grade in Singapore schools. It involves teaching students concepts using a three-stage learning process: concrete, pictorial, and abstract. In the concrete stage, students engage in hands-on learning experiences using physical objects which can be everyday items such as paper clips, toy blocks or math manipulates such as counting bears, link cubes and fraction discs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zearn Math</title>
      <link>/math/zearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/zearn/</guid>
      <description>Zearn   The first is excellent scaffolding: All lessons build from previous knowledge and spiral from accessing learned skills Thorough scaffolding and reinforcement of learned math skills Online math curriculum (coupled with live whole- and small-group instruction) for grades one through five, with supplemental skills practice activities for kindergartners. Number of warm-ups that promote number sense and skill-specific tactics Guided practice with interactive video lessons that feature enthusiastic human teachers and school-age children    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beast Academy</title>
      <link>/math/beast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/beast/</guid>
      <description>Take aways    Allows student to focus on math concepts they are strugglign with
  Self-paced material that might need some curation from the parent.
  Numerous videos and firums available to discuss math concepts/problems.
    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
