<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>math on Learnosity</title>
    <link>/categories/math/</link>
    <description>Recent content in math on Learnosity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Math Overview</title>
      <link>/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/</guid>
      <description>Math is important and it’s important to help young children develop their mathematical thinking. A child’s math knowledge at the start of kindergarten predicts later academic achievement better than early reading or attention skills. Math is part of children’s everyday lives. Taking advantage of each of these math moments develops math learning. Each math moment is like a charging station that helps children become ready for more math learning. Math is measuring, sorting, building, noticing patterns, making comparisons, and describing the environment, as well as counting and knowing the names of shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindergarten</title>
      <link>/math/kindergarten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/kindergarten/</guid>
      <description>Core Standard for Math - K  Website
 In Kindergarten, instructional time should focus on two critical areas: 1. representing and comparing whole numbers, initially with sets of objects  describing shapes and space. More learning time in Kindergarten should be devoted to number than to other topics.  IXL   Aligned to the Common Core State Standards or State standards Membership fees range from $9.95-$19.95 per month Math skills covered Continous Diagnostic tool helps identify what a student knows already and what they need to improve An app is available for iPad, Android, Chromebook, and Kindle Fire devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade 1</title>
      <link>/math/grade1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/grade1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade 2</title>
      <link>/math/grade2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/grade2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade 3</title>
      <link>/math/grade3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/grade3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade 4</title>
      <link>/math/grade4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/grade4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade 5</title>
      <link>/math/grade5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/grade5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore-Math</title>
      <link>/math/singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/singapore/</guid>
      <description>In typical U.S. math programs, students get a worked example, then solve problems that very closely follow that example, repeating all the same steps with different numbers.
Singapore math is a teaching method based on Singapore Ministry of Education national primary mathematics curriculum used for grade one through sixth grade in Singapore schools. It involves teaching students concepts using a three-stage learning process: concrete, pictorial, and abstract. In the concrete stage, students engage in hands-on learning experiences using physical objects which can be everyday items such as paper clips, toy blocks or math manipulates such as counting bears, link cubes and fraction discs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beast Academy</title>
      <link>/math/beast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/beast/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saxon Math</title>
      <link>/math/saxon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/saxon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Math</title>
      <link>/math/configuration-markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/math/configuration-markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
